Let's talk about the project management knowledge areas and I'm going to coordinate these with the different
chapters in the pinball.
So first off we have project integration management recall integration managements the gears of project
management.
This is cheaper for the Pinback guy.
It's where we do the processes of developing the charger.
Developing a project management plan directing and managing the project work managing project knowledge
monitoring control project work perform integrated change control have close the project or phase.
Then we go into scope management Chapter 5 in the head about Plan scope management collect requirements
to find scope create the UBS validate scope and control scope.
So those are the processes here in this knowledge area.
Schedule management Chapter 6 in a Pinback guy planned schedule management defined activities sequence
the activities estimate how long those activities will take develop and control schedule.
Those are the processes in chapter 6 cost management Krien that cost management plan.
This is Chapter 7 in the Pinback guide or first one there plan cost management estimate cost.
Determine your budget and control cost.
So those are the processes for cost management.
Next step is a little pop quiz for you Chapter 8 in the Pinback quality quality management plan quality
management manage quality and control quality.
So those are the processes in this knowledge area of quality management.
Chapter 9 resource management resource management.
We need a resource management plan.
Estimate activity resources acquire resources develop the team manage the team and control resources.
So Chapter 9 in the Pinback next Dubcek 10 just three processes and Chapter 10 on communications management
plan communications management manage communications and Monett church communications.
Those are the processes here risk management plan risk management identify risk do qualitative and quantitative
analysis.
Plan our responses.
Implement those responses and then monitor risk throughout the project.
So that's Chapter 11 and the Pinback guy our next knowledge area is on procurement procurement management.
Just three roll processes planned procurement management conduct procurement and control procurement.
So this is chapter 12 in the Pinback.
And then remember this guy.
Stakeholder management stakeholder management Chapter 13 identifying our stakeholders planning stakeholder
engagement managing stakeholder engagement and monitoring stakeholder engagement.
So those were our processes for stakeholder management.
You may be wondering well why are we going through these processes again and again and again and these
knowledge areas again and again and again.
Because it's important to recognize these processes and what we're doing is an approach that's called
the whole method that rather than just seeing little tiny segmented portions of course we're seeing
an exposure to all of the information as we move through the courts.
Once we get into past these introductory chapters in the Pinback which is really where we are now that
we get into chapters 4 and 5 and so on then we'll be pretty isolated over it will only talk about scope
or we'll only talk about quality.
So I don't you feel frustrated that we keep seeing the same types of stuff over and over we're just
looking at it from different angles.
This is part of the learning that you really need to be able to recognize these different components
and how it fits in.
So keep going you're doing great.
Stay with it you're learning you're building a solid base here.
And so when we get into later chapters it will help make the connection to how these processes are integrated.
All right I'll see you in the next lecture.